Guide to the Kenneth Walter Cameron Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Collection of Seals, 1860-1947; Series I; 0.1; (1/2 box)
  - SCRAPBOOKS
    - Volume IV. Seals of the United States (including state and departmental seals), seals of various consulates both here and abroad, and some seals of British colonial possessions, 1925-37
      Young, C. C. TLS, [Consul General of the Republic of China], TLS, New York, 1 p., Aug. 23, 1927
      Zimmerman, Fred R. TLS, Executive Chamber, Madison, Wisconsin, 1 p., Feb. 4, 1928
    - Volume V. Autographs, letters, and documents from the governors of the States and Territories of the U.S., and letters and seals from the Provinces of Canada, and the seal of the Dean of [Exeter Cathedral?], 1929-32
      Adams, William H. TNS, Denver, Colorado, 1 p., Sep. 22, 1931
      Blackwood, Ibra C. Autograph, written on official paper, Columbus, S. C., 1 p., Sep. 17, 1931
      Bryan, Charles Wayland. Autograph signature on card, enclosed in a TL signed by the Assistant Secretary to the Governor, Lincoln, Nebraska, Apr. 11, 1932
      Burgess, Harry. Autograph on a card, Balboa Heights, C. Z., Sep. 24, 1931
      Carlton, Doyle E. TNS and autograph on a card, Tallahassee, Fla., Sep. 18, 1931
      Case, Norman Stanley. Autograph on a card, Providence, R. I., Sep. 17, 1931
      Caulfield, Henry Stewart. Autograph signature on a card, Jefferson City, Mo., Sep. 1931
      Conley, William G. Autograph on a card, Charleston, W. Va., [Sep.? 1931]
      Davis, Dwight Filley. Autograph on a card, Manila, P. I., Sep. 10, 1931
      Dern, George Henry. TLS, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1 p., Sep. 19, 1931
      Erickson, John E. TLS, Helena, Mont., 1 p., Sep. 19, 1931
      Gardiner, William T. Autograph on a card bearing the Maine seal, n.d.
      Gardner, Oliver Max. Autograph on a piece of paper, [Raleigh, N. C.], 1 p., [Sep. 1931]
      Green Warren E. Autograph appended to KWC's letter to His Excellency Hon. Green, New York City, 1 p., Sep. 16, 1931
      Hunt, George Wylie Paul. Autograph signature on a card, Phoenix, Arizona, Sep. 19, 1931
      Judd, Lawrence M. Autograph on the official stationary, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1 p., [Oct? 1931]
      La Follette, Philip Fox. Autograph on a card, [Madison, Wis.], Sep. 17, 1931
      Leslie, Harry G. Autograph on a card, enclosed in a TNS by the Secretary to the Governor of Indiana, Indianapolis, Ind., 1 p., Sep. 25, 1931
      Long, Huey Pierce. TNS, Baton Rouge, La., 1 p., Sep. 17, 1931
      Meier, Julius L. Autograph, signing the description of the seal of the state of Oregon, [Salem, Ore.], 1 p., [Sep. 1931]
      Munroe, Hugh Edwin. Autograph on official stationary, Regina, Saskatchewan, 1 p., [Sep. 19? 1931]
      Murray, William Henry. Autograph on a card, [Oklahoma City, Okla.], n.d.
      Olson, Floyd B. Autograph, written on official paper, St. Paul, Minn., 1 p., [Sep. 1931]
      Parnell, Harvey. TNS, Little Rock, Ark., 1 p., Sep. 17, 1931
      Pearson, Paul Martin. TLS, St. Thomas, Virgin Islands, 1 p., Sep. 22, 1931
      Pinchot, Gifford. ALS, [Harrisburg, Pa., Sep. 16, 1931]
      Pollard, John Garland. Autograph written on the official stationary, [Richmond, Va.], 1 p., [Mar. 25, 1929]
      Ritchie, Albert Cabell. TNS enclosing a card autographed, and an autographed copy of Maryland's Flag, Seal, Flower, and Song, Annapolis, Md., Sep. 16, 1931
      Roosevelt, Franklin D. Autograph on a card, Albany, N. Y., [Sep. 1931]
      Roosevelt, Theodore. Autograph on an official card, Porto Rico, Nov. 4, 1931
      Root, Capt. Edmund Spence. Autograph on a slip of paper, [Naval Station, Guam], Sep. 16, 1931
      Ross, C. Ben. Autograph on a card, enclosed in a TN signed by the Secretary to the Governor of Idaho, Boise, Idaho, Sep. 19, 1931
      Ross, William Donald. TLS, Toronto, 1 p., Sep. 24, 1931
      Sampson, Flem D. TNS, Frankfort, Ky., 1 p., Sep. 19, 1931
      Seligman, Arthur. Autograph on a card, [Santa Fe, N. M., Sep. 1931]
      Shafer, George F. Autograph on a piece of note-paper, [Bismarck, N. D.], 1 p., [Sep. 18, 1931]
      Turner, Dan W. Autograph, written on a piece of note-paper, [Des Moines, Iowa], 1 p., [Sep. 1931]
      Winant. John Gilbert. Autograph on a card, [Concord, New Hampshire, Sep. 1931]
      Woodring, Harry H. Autograph, written on an autograph card, [Topeka, Kan., Sep. 1931]
- Autograph Collection of Church Figures, 1916-39; Series II; 0.1; (1/2 box)
  - Description of autograph collection by KWC, 1937 (Box 3)
  - Acheson, Edward Campion (Bishop). ALS to Bishop Edward M. Parker, Middletown, Connecticut, 1 p., 1916 Sep 9 (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Charles Palmerston (Bishop). Fragments of TLS to Bishop Edward M. Parker, Chicago, 1 p., 1920 Jan 10 (Box 5)
  - Athenagoras, Spyrou (Archbishop of North and South America). TLS to the Reverend William Chauncey Emhardt, Astoria, Long Island, 1 p., 1939 Jun 9 (Box 6)
  - Bell, George Kennedy Allen (Bishop). ALS (signed George Cicestr) to the Reverand William Chauncey Emhardt, The Palace, Chichester, 1 p., 1930 Jun 27 (Box 7)
  - Dallas, John T. Autograph signature, n.d. (Box 8)
    On a sheet of official diocesan paper, stanped with three seals of the Diocese of New Hampshire, and having also an impression in wax of the Bishop's coat-of-arms, made with his episcopal ring
  - Farthing, John Cragg (Bishop of Montreal). Autograph signature on a certificate of transfer for William David Armitage from the Diocese of Montreal to the Diocese of New Hampshire, 1 p., 1921 Mar 31 (Box 9)
  - Farthing, John Cragg (Bishop of Montreal). TLS to the Reverend Robert F. Lau, Montreal, 1 p., 1932 Sep 16 (Box 10)
  - Gore, Charles (Bishop of Oxford). ANS to the Reverend William C. Emhardt, London, 1 p. with address, 1930 Aug 13 (Box 11)
  - Gravatt, William Loyall. Autograph, on a Christmas card, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Jasinski, John Z. Printed invitation signed, to Robert F. Lau, Buffalo, New York, 1932 Jun 24 (Box 13)
  - Küry, Adolf (Bishop). TLS in German to Robert F. Lau, Bern, [Switzerland], 1925 Dec 19 (Box 14)
  - Papageorgopoulos, Kallistos (Bishop). TLS to William Chauncey Emhardt, Astoria, Long Island, 1 p., 1931 Jun 18 (Box 15)
  - Temple, William (Archbishop of Canterbury). TLS signed William Ebor, to William Chauncey Emhardt, Bishopthorpe, York, 1 p., 1931 Nov 21 (Box 16)
  - Walpole, George Henry Somerset (Bishop). ANS to Richard Kemp, Edinburgh, 1918 Feb 18 (Box 17)
  - White, William Charles (Bishop). 3 ALS signed "William Newfoundland" to Bishop Edward M. Parker, St John's, Newfoundland, 1922 (Box 18)
  - Williams, Lennox Waldron (Bishop of Quebec). Official Letters Testimonial filled out in his autograph, and signed by him as Lord Bishop of Quebec, 1 p., 1921 Jan 28 (Box 19)
- Collection of Historic Documents, 1753-1939; Series III; 0.8; (2 boxes)
  - Barry, George. ALS (facsimile), 1899 Easter (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Belknap, William W. ALS to General Grant, 1872 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bethune, George W. Four stanzas of verse, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Betts, John M. ALS to General Patrick, 1863 Dec 27 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bird, Isabella L. [signed Isabella Bishop] ALS to Mrs. Bompas, [n.y.] Weds (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bodnigfold, Rev. Bacon. Abstract of Will, 1797 May 14
  - Booth, Sir Thomas. Will, 1753 Dec 8?
  - Brough, Robert Barnabas. ANS to unidentified, 1850 Nov 26 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bullen, A. H. ALS to unidentified, 1910 Aug 19 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Burnand, Francis Cowley. ALS to Mr. Adams, 1891 Apr 21 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bury, Charlotte Campbell. ALS in the third person to Mr. Batendale, 1839 Jun 3 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cameron, J. [John?] Autograph clipped from a letter, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cameron, J. D. Autograph clipped from a letter, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Cameron, Simon. Autograph, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Canby, Henry Seidel. Autograph, and newspaper clipping of article and photograph of him, 1924 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Cantnor, Randall. ALS to Constance Satterlee, 1905 Jul 9 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chambers, W. & R. ALS to John Timbs, 1841 Jul 8? (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Clark, E. D. ALS to [Alaric Alexander?] Watts, [n.y.] Feb 15 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Clifford, Sophia Lucy Lane. ALS to Mr. Knowles, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Clive, Caroline Meysey-Wigley. ALS to Mr. Ford, [n.y.] Dec 7 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Coates, Joseph. ALS to Matthew Mills Coates, 1826 Apr 20
  - Cobbe, Frances Power. ALS to unidentified, [n.y.] Feb 6 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Colum, Padraic. Typescript poem, signed, entitled "The Plower", 1946 Oct 17 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Conwell, Russell Herman. Autograph clipped from a letter, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Corson, Juliet. ALS to Miss Booth, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cox, Samuel Sullivan. ALS to General W. L. Stone, 1885 Feb 10 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Coxe, A. Cleveland. Presentation inscription, 1889 Feb 9 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Creighton, Louise. 2 ALS to unidentified, 1914-15 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cromek, Thomas Hartley. Holograph copy, signed, of a poem by Charles Waterton, entitled "Shipwreck", 1843 Jun 17 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Del Hay, Peter. Copy of will of 1426 (2 versions), n.d.
  - Deranger, Louis W. ALS to Mr. Neimann, 1849 Apr 15 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Dewey, John. Autograph, 1939 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Diamond, Hugh Welch. ALS to A. Donadrin, 1845 Jun 20 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Dickinson, Anna Elizabeth. ALS to W. H. Cary, 1871 Mar 4 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Dilke, Charles Wentworth. ALS to Governor Gilpin, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Dowden, E. Presentation inscription in the third person, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Durant, Will. Autograph, 1938 Nov 29 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Erskine, John. Autograph, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Forbes, Archibald. ALS to Mr. Hill, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Forbes, D. ALS to Messrs. Allen & Co., 1837 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Forbes, Edward. ALS to W. H. Campbell, 1838 Jan 27 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Forbes, James. Autograph, a few lines clipped from a letter, and a newspaper clipping (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Forbes, James. ALS to William Hayley, 1805 Nov (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Freeman, Edward Augustus. 1 ALS to J. E. Bowen, a few lines from a letter[?], 1884 Apr 10 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Froud, James. ALS to Col. Payne, 1884 Nov 20 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Garcia, [M?]. ANS to unidentified, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Gatty, Mrs. Alfred. ALS to Miss Cramer, [n.y.] Weds (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Gerard, Dorothea. ALS to "My Dear Mary", 1901 Nov 24 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Gilfillan, George. ALS to unidentified, 1848 Sep 7 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Gough, John Ballentine. ALS to Rev. W. M. Martin, [n.y.] Aug 2 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Greene, Mary Anne Everett. ALS to unidentified, 1886 Sep 18 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Hall, Basil. Fragment of ALS, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Halstead, Murat. ALS to unidentified, 1885 Jan 17 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Hamilton, J. ALS to Mr. Bainbridge, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Haweis, Hugh Reginald. ALS to Mr. Stratton, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Hocking, Joseph. ALS to Mr. Guss, 1916 Feb 11 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Hoey, Frances Cashel. ALS to Mr. Bowkes, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Holbrook, Josiah. ALS to C. F. Cleveland, 1833 Apr 19 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Hold, Abel. ANS to J. P. Knight, 18[80?] May 16 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Holden, Hubert. ALS to unidentified, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Holdsworth, Annie E. ALS Mr. Smith, 1894 Jul 16 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Hole, S. Reynolds. ANS to unidentified, 1893 Aug 5 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Holland, Henry Scott. ALS to unidentified (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Holland, James. ALS to Dominic Paul Colnaghi, 1833 Aug 27 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Holmes, Basil. ANS to the Secretary of the Royal Academy, 1850 Jul 31 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Holmes, Richard P. ANS to Mrs. Lefray, 1869 Nov 11 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Holt, David. ALS to E. I. Neimann, 1848 Apr 16 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Holyoake, [George Jacob?]. ALS to Mr. Strahan, 1878 Oct 3 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Hook, Theodore E. ALS to unidentified, 1826 Jan 1 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Hope, John. Order to pay, 1807 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Hope, Thomas. ALS to unidentified, 1820 Apr 12 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Hopkins, J. B. ALS to Chales Welsh, 1880 Oct 23 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Hopley, Miss [Catherine Cooper?]. AL in third person to Mr. Welsh, 1880 May 25 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Hopper, ----. ALS to Messrs Durand Blakeway & Co., 1939 Nov 30 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Hopper, Thomas[?]. ALS to unidentified, 18[24?] May 13 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Hopson, Grace. ALS to unidentified, 1760 Aug 5 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Hornby, Dr. J. J. ALS to unidentified, 1890 Oct 29 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Horner, Leonard. ALS to Dr. Humphrey, Jun 27, 1853 and ALS to C. A. Wild, Oct 20, 1847, 1847, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Horsley, William. ALS to A. Pettett, 1823 Dec 27 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Houghton, Richard Monckton Milnes. ALS to Mr. Evarts, [n.y.] Dec 20 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Howitt, A. M. [Anna Mary?]. ALS to Mrs. Watts, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Howitt, Mary [Botham?]. Four lines of verse, signed, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Howitt, Richard. ALS to unidentified, 1835 Jun 15 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Howitt, William. Inscription, with autograph, 1844 Feb (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Howley, William. ALS to unidentified recipients, 1805 Oct 11 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Hyne, Cutliffe. ALS to W. M. Coller, 1897 Aug 16 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Jersey [Channel Islands] "order for settling the differences which have arised in Jersey between the Inhabitants and their Officers of that Garrison" (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Joachim, Joseph. ALS to Charles Hallé, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Kennan, George. TLS to Mr. Holt, 1913 Aug 31 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Kepp, James M. ALS to unidentified, 1848 Nov 17 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Kingsley, Fanny. ALS to Ernest Coleridge, 1877 Jul (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Knox, Thomas Wallace. ANS to unidentified, 1893 Sep 24 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Lemon, Mark. Receipt for pension due to "Mary Anne à Beckett", 1857 Apr 8 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Lucy, Henry W. 2 ALS to unidentified, 1874, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - McDonough, James P. "Muster-Out Roll", 1864
  - Mackenzie, Robert Shelton. ALS to James R. Phillips, 18[60?] Jan 29 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Mallock, William Hurrell. ALS to Mrs. William Wetmore Story, 1889 Nov 13 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Marsh, George Perkins. ALS to unidentified, 1848 Apr 15 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Marston, Westland. ALS to William Hepworth Dixon, Feb. 23, 1864 and ALS to Mr. Banks, Dec. 27, 1865, 1864-65 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Massey, Gerald. ALS to unidentified, [n.y.] Thurs (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Meynell, Wilfred. ALS to [Sir John] Hammerton, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Moore, Frank Frankfort. ALS to Mr. Langbridge, 1894 Jan 9 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Morton, David. Typescript copy of a poem, signed, entitled "Reporter" (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Muddock, J. E. ALS to unidentified, 1895 Jan 30 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Munkittrick, Richard Kendall. ALS to C. C. Hunt, 1893 Jan 5 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Munro, D. A. ALS to Col. Harvey, 1900 Feb 28 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Murchison, Roderick Impey. ANS to unidentified, 1886 Apr 27 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Myers, Frederic William Henry. ALS to Mr. Knowles, 1894 Oct 2 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Newton, Richard Heber. ALS to unidentified, 1886 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Nichols, John Gough. ALS to C. B. Woodman, [n.y.] Aug 26 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Oakley, Octavius. 2 ALS to Mr. Neimann, 1850 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Palfrey, John G. [Gorham?]. ALS to Benjamin Bussey Thatcher, 1840 Jun 28 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Peabody, Andrew Preston. ALS to unidentified, 1891 Apr 30 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Peabody, Oliver William Bourne. Signed receipt, 1843 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Penny, Virginia B. ALS to C. C. Hunt, 1893 Jan 4 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Piatt, Donn. ALS to Mr. Chamberlain, 1881 Sep 18 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Pickett, J. C. to J. H. Causten, 1843 Nov 25 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Prentice, George Denison. ALS to William P. Roberts, 1860 Oct 26 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Quincy, Edmund. ALS to Mr. [William Lloyd?] Garrison, 1876 Jan 27 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Rayner, Nancy. ALS to unidentified, 1851 Mar 17 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Rayner, S. ALS to unidentified, [n.y.] Thurs (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Ridge, W. Pett. ANS to Mr. Goss, [n.y.] Weds (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Roome, Charles. ALS to Hon. Levi P. Morton, 1882 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Ruggles, Samuel B. ALS to Hon. Edward Everett, 1856 Mar 15 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Russell, John. AL to Longman & Co., with their reply, 1822
  - Rye, Maria S. ALS to unidentified, 1873 Apr 3 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Sadler, Michael Thomas. ALS to Rev. J. C. Franks, 1833 Dec 11 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Sangster, M. E. [Margaret Elizabeth Munson?]. ALS to Miss Booth, [n.y.] Mar 29 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Saunders, Frederick. ALS to General J. G. Wilson, 1891 Oct 15 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Savage, James. ALS to Henry Savage, 1855 May 12 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Schaff, Philip. ALS to Mr. Munro, 1882 May 22 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Schott, Charles A. ALS to Dr. Isaac Israel Hayes, 1862 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Seaman, Owen. 2 ALS to unidentified, 1911, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Sellar, Eleanor (Dennistoun). ALS to Miss Mair, [n.y.] Jun 8 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Shearman, Thomas Gaskel. ALS to unidentified, 1881 Sep 21 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Shepard, Edward Morse. ALS to Mr. Holt, 1905 Jul 11 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Sherburne, John Henry. ALS to unidentified, 1818 May 19
  - Sherwood, Lizzie. ALS to Mr. Ruggles, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Sherwood, Margaret [Pollock?]. ALS to the editors of the North American Review, 1913 Dec 13 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Siddons, F. Scott. ALS (on envelope) to G. H., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Smalley, George Washburn. ALS to unidentified, 1890 Sep 30 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Smithwick, Samuel. ALS to unidentified, 1825 Sep 28 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Squier, Ephraim George. ALS to C. G. Nicholson, 1871 Dec 9 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Sprague, Mary Alpin. ALS to Mr. Osgood, 1880 Dec 18 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Sprague, William Buell. ALS to Henry W. Ducachet, 1858 Dec 4 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Stanley, Arthur Penrhyn. ALS to Mrs. William Wetmore Story, 1868 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Stansbury, Arthur J. ALS to unidentified, 1847 Sep 3 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Stanton, Henry B. [Brewster?]. ALS to William P. Fessenden, 1862 Jan 23 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Straus, Isidor. TLS to Messrs. A. N. Marquis & Co., 1901 Jan 23 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Strickland, Agnes. ALS to Mr. Roberts, [1842 Mar 28] (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Stuart, Esmé B. ALS to Mrs. Ferreboschi, 1894 Aug 21 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Thevenot, Jacques fils. ALS in French to "Monsieur Le Duc de Lauzun Gouverneur Du Senegal", 1779 Mar 30 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Thwaites, Alice. Copy of will of 1485, n.d.
  - Toulmin, Camilla Du Four. ALS to Mrs. Banks, 1878 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Trafford, Cecil. Copy of will of 1673, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Tupper, Martin Farquhar. ALS to Dr. Wylie, 1881 Mar 21 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Tuttiett, Mary Gleed. ALS to unidentified, 1902 Feb 16 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Tweedie, Alexander. ANS to Mrs. Bompas, [n.y.] Feb 4 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - "Variétés: Une visite à la Grange- Bléneau en 1827," holograph manuscript, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Vavasor, Richard. Copy of will of 1618, n.d.
  - Vavasour, William. Copy of will, n.d.
  - Voysey, Charles. ALS to unidentified, 1895 Mar 4 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Watts, Alaric Alexander. Fragment of ALS incl. clipping and copy of portrait (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Whibley, Charles. 3 ALS to Mr. Knowles, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Whiteing, Richard. 2 ALS to Mr. Applegate, Jul 8, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Whitfield, Clarke. ALS to Mssrs. Lonsdale & Mills, 1834 Feb 17 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Williams, Nicholas. Will, 1840 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Winthrop, Robert. ALS to Gaylord Clark, 1839 Dec 27 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Winton, Randall. TLS to Bishop Satterlee, 1901 Feb 8 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary. ALS to unidentified, [n.y.] Apr 4 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Unidentified letters, 4 pieces, 1871, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - 6 engravings and one photocopy from magazine of a letter from Booth Tarkington to Senator Van Nuys, 1777-94, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 181)
- Personal Papers, 1927-32; Series IV; 0.2; (1 box)
  - Check, in KWC's autograph, payable to the Rt. Rev. William Loyall Gravatt, Wheeling, West Virginia, 1932 Dec 3 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - "The Channel Islands: A Brief Historical and Governmental Review of the Most Interesting of the Vestigal Remains of the Past," by KWC, 1929-30 (Box 4, Folder 183-186)
  - Three Zoology notebooks, signed, kept by KWC while a student at West Virginia University, 1927-28 (Box 4, Folder 187-189)
- Oversize, 5.9; (7 boxes)
  Oversize contains material from Series I and III
  - "Description of the Collection of Seals" (from Series I), 1937 Apr 4 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Printed material (from Series I), 1946-47, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Dominion of Canada. Animated atlas (from Series I), [1926?] (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Large Facsimile of the great seal of Puerto Rico (from Series I), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Seal of the United States General Land Office (from Series I), 1860, 1872 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Official copy of a certificate of incorporation of the Wheeling and Bridgeport Ohio Railway Company (from Series I), 1867 Oct 8 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Bodnigfold, Rev. Bacon. Abstract of Will (from Series III), 1797 May 14 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Booth, Sir Thomas. Will (from Series III), 1753 Dec 8? (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Coates, Joseph. ALS to Matthew Mills Coates (from Series III), 1826 Apr 20 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Del Hay, Peter. Copy of will of 1426 (2 versions) (from Series III), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - McDonough, James P. "Muster-Out Roll" (from Series III), 1864 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Russell, John. AL to Longman & Co., with their reply (from Series III), 1822 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Sherburne, John Henry. ALS to unidentified (from Series III), 1818 May 19 (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Thwaites, Alice. Copy of will of 1485 (from Series III), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Vavasor, Richard. Copy of will of 1618 (from Series III), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Vavasour, William. Copy of will (from Series III), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Wax seal of the Isle of Jersey, Channel Islands (from Series I) (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Wax seal of the Isle of Guernsey, Channel Islands (from Series I) (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Wax seal of Gambia Colony and Protectorate (from Series I) (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Volume I. Great seals of the states, territories, etc. of the United States (from Series I), 1924 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Volume II. Seals of the British Empire (from Series I), 1925-29 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Volume III. Seals of the British Empire, and the United States (from Series I), 1925-27 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Volume IV. Seals of the United States (from Series I), 1925-37 (Box 10, Folder 212)
  - Volume V. Autographs, letters, and documents from the governors of the States and Territories of the U.S. (from Series I), 1929-32 (Box 11, Folder 213)
  - "The Roll of the Highland Clans of Scotland" (from Series I) (Box bsd, folder 214)